Olajumoke Adetunji Human Resource Manager

ADDRESS

No 8, Kuramo Crescent Ocean Bay Estate By Orchid Road, Eleganza,

Lekki, Lagos

EMAIL

ayojumide@gmail.com

PHONE

08134712496, 08086789649

Profile

To utilize my skills, knowledge and experiences to bring out effective and organized office administration, and to ensure continuous improvement of organizational efficiency and progressive growth through high interpersonal relationships with colleagues and quality services to all customers and clients.

Education

Jan 2013 - Jul 2017

University of Lagos

Bachelor of Science Employment Relations & Human Resource

Management

Oct 2018 - Oct 2019

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)

Employment History

Jan 2019 - Sep 2019

LAGOS

Executive Assistant / Client Relations Executive

Dillon Consultants Nigeria Limited

- · Handled client's concerns and complaints.
- · File management and research.
- · Facilitated communication and relations with existing and prospective clients.
- · Attended to client's inquiries with prompt feedback and assistance.
- · Ensured timely and efficient management of office supplies
- · Record keeping and bookkeeping

Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

Human Resources Officer

LAGOS

Patovie Nigeria Limited

- · Provided support where necessary to staff.
- · Organized interviews for prospective employees.
- · Maintained employee records and documents.
- Researched and advised on employment regulations.

Jul 2018 - Oct 2018

Front Desk / Administrative Officer

LAGOS

Rich Lustre Colours

- · Maintained and updated records and inventory of raw materials and cars.
- · Supervised performance of staff.
- · Interacted with clients and potential clients.
- Created and managed the CEO's schedule and calendar.

Mar 2018 - Jun 2018

LAGOS

Customer Relationship Executive

Entefrica

- · Facilitated relations with existing and prospective clients.
- · Expanded existing clientele base
- · Addressed and attended to customers' concerns and complaints.
- Carried out customer satisfaction surveys

Skills

multi-tasking

Microsoft Office

Data and document management

• •

Good time management

Interpersonal Relationships



Hobbies

Travelling and networking

References

References available upon request